<krpano version="1.0.8" onstart="startup();">

	<!-- text style for hover info -->
	<textstyle name="hoverstyle" origin="center" yoffset="200" textalign="center" background="false" border="false" fontsize="30" textcolor="0xFFFFFF" bold="false" effect="glow(0xFFFFFF,0.7,4,2);glow(0x000000,1,4,2);dropshadow(3,45,0x000000,2,0.6);" showtime="0.1" fadetime="0.2" fadeintime="0.2" />

	<action name="startup">
		loadscene(about, null, MERGE, BLEND(1))
	</action>

<autorotate enabled="true"
            waittime="1.5"
            speed="3.0"
            />
 
<events onmousedown="action(globalmousedown)" /> 

	<action name="initialize">

		tween(plugin[directions].alpha,1.0,3)
	</action>
	
<action name="globalmousedown">
	set(hotspot[abouthotspot].alpha,1);
	set(hotspot[trailerhotspot].alpha,1);
	set(hotspot[entryhotspot].alpha,1);
	set(hotspot[bloghotspot].alpha,1);
</action>
                   
	<scene name="about">

	<progress
		showwait="none"
		/>

	<view 
		hlookat="0.0"
	  fov="65.0"
	  fovmax="90.0"
	  fovmin="45.0"
	  />

	<control usercontrol = "all"
		mousetype="drag2d"
	 	keycodesin  =""
	 	keycodesout =""
	 	/>
	 	<image>
				<cube url="../images/panos/about/pano_%s.jpg" />
			<tablet>
				<cube url="../images/panos/about/pano_%s.jpg" />
			</tablet>
		</image>

		<hotspot name="about1"
			url="plugins/textfield.swf"
			atv="-30"
			edge="top"
			width="500"
			height="320"
			html="data:htmlabout1"
			css="data:cssdata1"
			background="true"
			backgroundcolor="0x000000"
			backgroundalpha="0.5"
			capture="false"
			/>

		<hotspot name="about2"
			ath="90"
			atv="-30"
			edge="top"
			url="plugins/textfield.swf"
			width="500"
			height="388"
			html="data:htmlabout2"
			css="data:cssdata1"
			background="true"
			backgroundcolor="0x000000"
			backgroundalpha="0.5"
			capture="false"
			/>

		<hotspot name="about3"
			ath="180"
			atv="-30"
			edge="top"
			url="plugins/textfield.swf"
			width="500"
			height="550"
			html="data:htmlabout3"
			css="data:cssdata1"
			background="true"
			backgroundcolor="0x000000"
			backgroundalpha="0.5"
			capture="false"
			/>

		<hotspot name="about4"
			ath="-90"
			atv="-30"
			edge="top"
			url="plugins/textfield.swf"
			width="500"
			height="385"
			html="data:htmlabout4"
			css="data:cssdata1"
			background="true"
			backgroundcolor="0x000000"
			backgroundalpha="0.5"
			capture="false"
			/>

		<data name="htmlabout1">
			<p>
			<br />OFFSHORE is an interactive web documentary about the next chapter of oil: <b>'Extreme Oil' some call it or "Cowboy Drilling."</b><br />
			<br />
      <b>There are huge, untapped reserves of oil and gas beneath the world's oceans, 90 billion barrels in the Arctic alone. </b>As conventional sources of oil continue to dramatically decline, everyone from Scottish 'minnows' to international oil majors to the governments of Sierra Leone and Greenland wants in on the game.<br />
    	<br />
    	Yet this new oil frontier comes with <b>incredible risk — financial, environmental and social.</b></p>
		</data>
		<data name="htmlabout2">
      <p><br />On April 20th, 2010, the Deepwater Horizon drilling rig exploded triggering one of the world's worst environmental disasters, a calamity that continues to this day.<br />
      <br />
			The disaster brought the world’s attention to the patchily regulated, frequently invisible, world of offshore drilling. And it is ramping up: in the Gulf of Guinea, off the coasts of Russia, Iran, Brazil, in the Gulf of Mexico, offshore in Barbados and Mozambique. In the summer of 2012, while North America endured record heat waves and scientists warned us of tipping points and run-away climate change, two Shell drilling rigs, the Kulluk and the Discover set sail to drill exploratory wells off the shores of the North Slope of Alaska. Now, it’s only a matter of time before a new ‘great game’ opens in the pristine waters of the U.S. and Canadian Arctic.<br /> 
			<br />
			Opponents passionately believe <b>that it is not a case of "if" another oil spill occurs but "when."</b> 
</p>
		</data>
		<data name="htmlabout3">
      <p><br />Are we witnessing <b>the last chapter in the age of petroleum </b> where all risks become acceptable?<br /> 
      <br />
			<b>Are we trapped in a carbon labyrinth </b> where no escape seems possible?<br />
			<br />
			As communities in Louisiana, Brazil and Nigeria reel from recent oil spills, and as the prospect of Arctic drilling ignites a global debate, activists and local residents are mobilizing, using a variety of inventive tactics. OFFSHORE invites viewers on a complex journey through this new frontier where a profound struggle is evolving with huge stakes for the planet’s future.<br />
			<br />
			From the oil soaked shores of Louisiana to Brazil, from the Gulf of Guinea to Sakhalin Island and Alaska, meet fisherfolk, whistleblowers, geologists, indigenous communities and rigworkers, struggling for survival on <b>the last hydrocarbon frontier of the 21st century.</b><br />
			<br />
			Working with local photographers, artists and filmmakers, we are building a collaborative and immersive experience that is ongoing, current and urgent.
</p>
		</data>
		<data name="htmlabout4">
      <p><br />OFFSHORE is created by Brenda Longfellow, Glen Richards and Helios Design.<br />
      <br />
      Helios Production Team:<br />
      <br />
      <ul>
        <li>Producer: Sarah Arruda</li>
        <li>Interactive/Technical Director: Mike Robbins</li>
        <li>Creative Director: Alex Wittholz</li>
        <li>Graphic Design: Felix Wittholz, Joanna Durkalec</li>
        <li>Web Programming: Mike Robbins, Daniel Sundy</li>
        <li>3D Programming: Matt Brushett, Marc Pannozzo</li>
      </ul> 
      <br />
      Sound and Music Design: Phil Strong<br />
    	Consultant/ Story Editor: John Jordan<br />
			International Collaborators: Greenpeace, U.S.<br />
</p>
		</data>

		<data name="cssdata1">
			p {
				color: #ffffff;
				fontFamily: Helvetica, Arial, sans-serif;
				fontSize: 16;
				leading: 7;
				marginLeft: 20;
				marginRight: 20;
			}
		</data>


	</scene>

</krpano>